[{"answer": "I was doing a lieutenant colonel and I was doing fairly well in the Army, but I had no idea what the Army had in store for me.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "When you were here as a young, fresh-faced Colin Powell, what was the big dream for you?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "It's a great military.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "You as we sit here on Veterans Day in particular, what do you feel about the view of the modern American military?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Somebody will show up.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Do you feel that you need another Gerald Ford intervention?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Well, you know, you can't put it all on one individual.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "What advice would you give him to get America back on its feet right now in the modern world?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "It's not happening now because it's been made too difficult.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Why is it not happening?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "No, I'm not blaming you.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "You're going to blame me, are you?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Well, I don't play golf, so I wouldn't have got on the golf course.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Would you take that approach?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "I means go hide in your -- in your bunker so that people can't get to you, and then come out and fight in the streets.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Can you clarify that?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Well, the advice I'd give to the president, which I still do on occasion, I keep private.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "What do you think you should be advising him as someone who supported him about how to go back into the election fray?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "I was in my home, and I heard the news.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Where were you when you heard that bin Laden had been killed?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Did you admire the president for the sheer audacity of the decision-making of that?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "I don't think the two can be that easily compared.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "The huge difference in cost not just in human life but financially to America?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "I mean do you feel that you were in some way used?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "It's a remarkable democratic system we have.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "What do you make of it all?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I'm watching it as an American.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "I mean are you watching it as a Democrat or Republican?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "I would never make that decision now.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "If the election was tomorrow, and it will be in a year, and would you vote for Barack Obama as things stand again?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "You think more may pop up?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "I mean could we possibly see yourself?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "I rejected that 16 years ago, and I've given more than one explanation for it.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Are you really?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "It was me.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Was it your wife in the end who decided?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "It was you, not your wife?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Stick to being on television.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Am I a good shrink or bad shrink?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Are you more moderate by nature?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "I've known Mr. Cain for -- oh, I guess, known Herman for 15, 16 years.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "What do you make of Herman Cain?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I'm not going to get in to all of these claims.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Is it the man you recognize with all these claims?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Very well.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Do you remember that?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "We didn't have any money and I was going to Vietnam.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "How did you get out of that?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "No, I'm just --", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Where do you get this from?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Getting along.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "What's the secret of a happy marriage?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "OWELL: Service to others, service to something greater than yourself, service to country, serving a purpose in life.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "What are the key values to you that you think most people should really have as priorities?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Well, they were proud of me.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "What were your parents have made of your career?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Do you really?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Well, I was -- I was born in Harlem to immigrant parents, and my parents always had a job.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Do you think they're misguided?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "You said before with foreign policy that America should avoid saying we are going to instill our democracy on everybody.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "How do we get businesses that have a lot of money stacked up, how do we get them to invest that money and create jobs?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "I never answer single greatest or worst a questions.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "When you look back on it, excluding the obvious, children's births and marriage and so on, what's the single greatest moment of your life?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "I'm so enormously proud of all of those who are serving now and all of those who served in the past.", "docId": "111110pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "What message would you give them on this particular day?", "qSentId": 559}]